Front-End Developer

Tetiana Urupa

I have 9 years of experience as a GIS engineer. I'm sure my previous skills will help me a lot to become a professional as Front-End Developer.I have a passion for programming and I'm growing day by day. I like solving various tasks and applying new solutions to my websites.

View portfolio

Work Experience

Geo Marketing expert Sofrecom

May 2019 - March 2021 | Saudi Arabia (remote)

- Produced "as-built" drawings and other deliverables (Excel and AutoCad documents for the transformation to GIS)
- · Creating the fiber optic scheme on the map with clients data
- · Digitalization existing governmental cadastral map
- Data preparation for a marketing survey. Processing these data after field's work
- · Remote management of fibre surveyors team
- · Reporting and communication with client

Co-founder/Project Manager Vmaps

September 2016 - September 2018 | Ukraine

- Managment processes in GIS projects (maps/orthophoto plans creating/updating for telecommunication and civil needs)
- Post-process collected drone data. Verify the accuracy of aerial data.
 Preparing reports.
- · Working on updating address information for navigation
- · Technical tasks creating

GIS Operator Visicom

September 2013 - September 2016 | Ukraine

- · Digitalization and processing vector data regarding client's needs
- · Checking and compiling data for digital maps different scales

Education

BeetRoot Academy

Front-End Developer

07.2022 - 11.2022

Kiev National University of Construction and Architecture

Geographical informational systems and technologies

September 2009 – June 2013

Tech Skills

- HTML
- CSS / SCSS
- JavaScript
- Vue.js
- Git / GitHub
- Gulp
- Figma
- ArcGis
- MapInfo
- QGIS
- AutoCad
- FME

Languages

- English Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Fluent
- Portuguese Beginner

Contacts

Tel: +351 932 324 581

E-mail: taniaivanko@ukr.net